Melanie Callor Bott

I am organized and efficient and work hard to expand my knowledge and abilities. I work with customers daily through face-to-face contact as well as online. I am experienced in customer service and business management, with over 20 years experience. I am an experienced Marketing Director with ten years experience in branding and marketing businesses. I thrive when taking on challenges and feel that challenges are the best source of growth for an indiviudal and business.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SPRINGVILLE-MAPLETON CHAMBER OF COMMERCE

PRESIDENT 2019-PRESENT EXECUTIVE BOARD 2016-PRESENT

MOUNTAIN WEST ANIMAL HOSPITAL

MARKETING DIRECTOR 2013-PRESENT CFO/HOSPITAL ADMINISTRATOR

-First Place Best of Utah County (2013-2020)

BOTT VETERINARY SERVICES & CONSULTING

MARKETING DIRECTOR 2009-2017
ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

Coding Boot Camp

Full Stack Web Developer

2020-PRESENT

WASHINGTON STATE UNIVERSITY

Graduate Certificate in Health
Communication and Promotion

2020-PRESENT

WASHINGTON STATE UNIVERSITY

M.S. in Strategic Communication 2017–2019
Honor Society

WASHINGTON STATE UNIVERSITY

B.A. in Human Development 2006–2009 Honor Society



(801) 669-0451
melaniebottegmail.com
Mapleton, UT 84664
www.linkedin.com/in/melaniecallor-bott-77ab7661/

SKILLS

Brand Recognition
Marketing & Web Design
Visual Media
HTML, CSS, Javascript, AJAX
Sequelize, Node.js, Express.js
SQL, Heroku, Firebase, Git
Communication:

Communication:

Business Communication

Customer Service

Online Communication

Crisis Communication

Project Management

Data Entry

Bookkeeping

Payroll Quickbooks

Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Google Applications

Adobe Spark, Illustrator, InDesign

Wordpress

Wix, Canva, Word Press Blackboard, Canvas